star health ipo opens can the rakesh
junjianwala touch protect your portfolio
new delhi the ipo of star health and
allied insurance company kicked off for
subscription on tuesday the rakesh
gingen walla backed firm is signed to
raise as much as 7 249 rupees crore via
primary route at the upper end of the
price band the company is valued at
nearly 5.9 times its assets under
management as on september 30th the ipo
consists of fresh equity shares up to
2000 rupees crore and an offer for sale
of up to 58 million 324 225 shares star
health a standalone health insurer
commands a market share of 15.8 percent
in the segment in terms of size strong
growth and gross written premium and
better operational performance analysts
said considering september 30th 2021
adjusted bvps of 90.35 rupees on the
post-issue basis the company is going to
list at a p b of 9.96 with a market cap
of 51
796.1 rupees crore it added the
valuations commanded by star health at
5.5 x 21 cap to gross written premium
which is in line with recent deals in
the standalone health insurance space
and appears fair considering its
positioning said angel 1 recommending to
subscribe it from a long-term
perspective only